picollecta.com 2014-03-31

# Privacy Policy | Picollecta

**Picollecta Privacy Policy**

Fraser Investments Limited are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with our [terms of use](http://picollecta.com/page/Terms-and-conditions-of-use-68) and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (“Act”), the data controller is Fraser Investments Limited of 5 Strand House, The Strand, St. Peter Port, Guernsey GY1 1LJ 

1 **Definitions:  **

1.1 Unless otherwise defined in this Policy, terms in this Policy have the same meanings as in our [terms and conditions of use](http://picollecta.com/page/Terms-and-conditions-of-use-68).

1.2 In all Policies we will refer to Fraser Investments Limited as “ **Picollecta** ”, “ **our** ”, “ **us** ” or “ **we** ”. 

**2 Information we may collect from you:**

2.1 We may collect and process the following data about you:

• Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site picollecta.com (“our site”). This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site, subscribing to our service, posting material or requesting further services. 

• In particular, on registration to the Service you will need to  provide personal information. Picollecta creates a user account for use of the Service based on the personal information you provide. This personal information can include first and last name, email address, Profile Picture, Country of Residence. We will use this data to provide you with the Services.

• Email addresses will also be required from you so that we can confirm your registration and communicate with you regarding Picollecta newsletters, marketing and promotional  material that may be of interest to you.  

• You also have the option to import your personal contacts (including email addresses) so that you can invite friends to join you on our site. 

• We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site.

• If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

• We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.  

• Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, and the resources that you access. 

**3 IP Addresses : **

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

**4 Cookies: **

Part of our Service requires us to use technological tools including, but not limited to, cookies. Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when using our website and allows us to improve our site. For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them see our [Cookie policy](http://picollecta.com/page/Cookie-Policy-73).

**5 Where we store your Personal Data: **

5.1 The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy. 

5.2 All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

5.3 Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

5.4 We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties. 

**6 Uses Made Of The Information: **

6.1 We use information held about you in the following ways:

• to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;

• to provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes;

• to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us;

• to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so; and 

• to notify you about changes to our service.

6.2 We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these by post or telephone. 

6.3 If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which we have provided you with. 

6.4 If you are a new customer, and where we permit selected third parties to use your data, we (or they) will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this. 

6.5 If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data on the registration form).

6.6 We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, women in SW1). We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience.

**7 Third Parties:**

7.1 Our site may from time to time, contain links to and from other platforms and providers (for example Facebook). If you follow a link to any of these websites please note that they have their own privacy policies. We do not accept responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before submitting any personal data to or through these websites.

7.2 Our site also offers the opportunity for you to register with your log in details from other platforms and providers, i.e. through Facebook. With your consent the platform provider will transfer personal data to us which may include, but is not limited to, Name, profile picture, sex, user ID, birth date. This transferred data is used to create a User Profile on our site for Picollecta. You may at any time revoke your consent by informing us at Fraser Investments Limited at 5 Strand House, The Strand, St. Peter Port, Guernsey GY1 1LJ or info@picollecta.com or, by modifying your privacy settings on the platform provider. For full details on the extent of the collection and usage of this data please see the terms of use and privacy policy on the respective platform provider’s website. 

7.3 When you register for the Service and submit personal information to create a profile, other Service users will see your chosen user name. If you choose to complete the profile description this will also be visible to other Service users. Providing additional information within the Settings of your profile is voluntary and should correlate to the level of interaction you wish to have with other Service users. We recommend you guard and refrain from disclosing any information you consider private and confidential. 

7.4 Picollecta may at times employ third party companies to facilitate our Service, including but not limited to, maintenance services, database management and web analytics. These third parties have access to users’ personal information solely to perform these tasks and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

7.5 We may share information within your Picollecta account with the other platforms and providers that you have linked to your Picollecta account (i.e. Facebook). These third parties have access to your personal information only for this purpose. 

**8 Your Rights: **

8.1 You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at Fraser Investments Limited at 5 Strand House, The Strand, St.Peter Port, Guernsey GY1 1LJ or info@picollecta.com. You can also manage your email preferences within the Settings of your profiles at picollecta.com.

8.2 Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. As explained above at paragraph 7 (Third Parties), if you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

**9 Disclosure of your Information: **

9.1 We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.

9.2 We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

9.2.1 in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;

9.2.2 if Fraser Investments Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets;

9.2.3 if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our [terms of use](http://picollecta.com/page/Terms-and-conditions-of-use-68) and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Fraser Investments Limited, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**10 Access to Information: **

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

**11 Changes to our Privacy Policy: **

Any changes made to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

**12 Contact: **

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to Fraser Investments Limited at 5 Strand House, The Strand, St.Peter Port, Guernsey GY1 1LJ or info@picollecta.com.
